brazilianbikinishop.com 2017-09-08

# Terms and Conditions

## Index:

## Legal Notice

**Tel** : (786) 224-0188 (Our customer services team will be happy to answer your questions any time from 2 p.m. to�11 p.m., Monday to Friday)   
**Email** : info@brazilianbikinishop.com

 **Company name�:** Brazilian Bikini Shop S.A.R.L.

**Companies Register Number :** R.C.S. ANTIBES 509778270�  
**Date of incorporation�:** 08 January 2009  
**Registered Capital�:** 7500 �  
**EU VAT number :** FR 36 509778270

**Editorial Director�:** M. Guatteri Gian Marco  
**Our Translation Partner :** Dixit.com

**Head Office**  
Brazilian Bikini Shop S.A.R.L.   
75, Chemin des Collettes,   
06800 Cagnes sur mer,  
C�te D'azur - French Riviera, France

**Return Address - USA**  
Brazilian Bikini Shop  
1033 SW 30TH AVE   
DEERFIELD BEACH   
FL 33442   
United States

**Return Address - Europe**  
Brazilian Bikini Shop S.A.R.L.  
Monique van Luijk  
Chemin de Peyrecave  
09600 Regat  
France

**Return Address - Canada:**  
Brazilian Bikini Shop   
5810 AMBLER DRIVE UNIT 10  
MISSISSAUGA  
ONTARIO L4W4J5   
Canada

**Return Address - Italy:**  
Brazilian bikini shop C/o SDA  
ImperiaVia Argine dx snc  
18100 Imperia  
Italia

**Return Address - Portugal:**  
Elisabete Coelho  
Brazilian Bikini Shop  
Rua Sao Tome e Principe Lote 14-M 3 esq.  
2950-114 Palmela  
Portugal

## Terms and Conditions

Last update 23/06/2017

Local address are also available in Germany, India, Brazil and other countries. Contact the customer service to get more information

### **1\. INFORMATION ABOUT US**

This site is operated by and the goods you purchase will be supplied by Brazilian Bikini Shop S.a.r.l. ("we").  
We are registered in Antibes, France under company number RCS 509778270 and with our registered office at 75 Chemin des Collettes, 06800 Cagnes sur mer, C�te D�Azur, France. Our main trading address is Brazilian Bikini Shop S.a.r.l, 75 Chemin des Collettes, 06800 Cagnes sur mer, C�te D�Azur, France. Our VAT number is FR 36 509778270.

**Customer Service** :  
You can contact us by email at info@brazilianbikinishop.com,   
by telephone on (786) 224-0188 - Monday to Friday from 2 PM to 23h PM (Paris Time zone)

### **2\. YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We will use your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy (Read our �[Privacy Policy](http://www.brazilianbikinishop.com/en/viewpage/terms-and-conditions-41.html#privacy "Privacy information")� page), which forms part of these terms.

### **3\. CONTRACT CONCLUSION**

If you submit an order for goods via this site by clicking 'Submit order', your order is an offer to us to buy the goods on our website.  
We will acknowledge receipt of your order by sending you an automatically generated email accepting your order. With this email the contract will be concluded.  
The contract will relate only to those specific goods which are referred to in our email confirming our acceptance of your order. You should read and check the details in this email to ensure that they are correct.  
If the details in the email confirming your order are not correct, or if you are not satisfied with the details in the email, please contact us at info@brazilianbikinishop.com.  
The contractual language is English.  
We store the contract�s content and will send you the details of your order as well as the our general terms via e-mail. The general terms you can find at page �General terms� at all times.  
The details about your recent orders you will find in your customer login.

### **4\. PRICE AND DELIVERY COSTS**

We shall use our reasonable endeavours to ensure that the prices as quoted on our site are correct.  
Information displayed on this site relating to pricing is subject to change by us without notice, but those on the site at the time of any order placed will be the prices applicable to that order.  
Where the correct price of the goods is less than our stated price, we will charge the lower amount on dispatch. If the correct price of the goods is higher than the price stated on our site, we may, if possible, reject your order in our discretion, in which case we will notify you of such rejection and the correct price for the goods.  
Unless stated otherwise, all prices include VAT (where applicable) but exclude delivery costs.  
Delivery costs can be looked up here <http://www.brazilianbikinishop.com/en/viewpage/shipping-13.html>. They will be notified to you separately before you submit your order and will be confirmed to you by email.

Shipment to countries outside of the European Union may be subject to taxes, customs duties and fees levied by the destination country ("Import Fees"). The recipient of the shipment is the importer of record in the destination country and is responsible for all Import Fees.

### **5\. AVAILABILITY AND DELIVERY**

Information displayed on this site relating to availability is subject to change by us without notice.  
We cannot guarantee permanent or continuous availability of all products on this site. All orders are subject to availability at all times.  
We deliver any countries: Europe, UK, USA and any other countries.  
We will deliver the goods ordered by you to the address you give us for delivery at the time you make your order on the site.  
Delivery will be made according to the information on the product pages after your order is accepted.  
We are not responsible for any delay in delivery caused by the unavailability of someone to take delivery of the products. It is your responsibility to contact the post office or courier company as applicable to arrange the collection or delivery of products that could not be delivered because you were unavailable.

### **6\. PAYMENT**

Payment for goods can be made by one of the following payment methods  
\- Bank Payment  
\- Visa, MasterCard, American Express  
\- PayPal  
\- Credit card through Paypal  
\- Debit card through Paypal  
Payment for goods will be made in accordance with the procedure explained in the information page �payment methods�.  
Please note that if your credit card or bank account is in a different currency than Euros, your credit card company or bank may apply currency conversion costs.

### **7\. RIGHT TO CANCEL**

Exchanges are possible until **100 days** , beginning from the purchase date.

You have the right to cancel the purchase of a good without having to give a reason at any time within the �cooling off period� of 30�days�from the purchase date (Or�within 14 days after you receive the goods, if your order is delivered�later than 16 days�after the purchase date).  
You must notify us of your cancellation in writing or in another durable medium to our contact address.   
Cancellation consequences  
If you are in possession of the goods you are under the duty to retain them and take reasonable care of them.

You must send the goods back to us in their original condition to our contact address at your own cost (unless we delivered the item to you in error or the item is damaged or defective) as soon as possible once you have cancelled the contract.  
We reserve the right to make a charge not exceeding our direct costs of recovering the goods if you do not return the goods or return them at our expense.

Once you have notified us that you wish to cancel the contract, any sum debited to us will be refunded to you as soon as possible and in any event within 14 days of your cancellation.

### **8\. REFUNDS POLICY**

When you return goods to us because you have cancelled the contract between us during the cooling-off period we will process the refund due to you as soon as possible and, in any case, within 14 days of the day you have given notice of your cancellation. We will refund the price of the goods in full, including the cost of sending the item to you. However, you will be responsible for the cost of returning the item to us.  
If you are not satisfied with a product for any reason e.g. if it is not what you ordered, it is damaged or defective, or we have delivered an incorrect quantity, please return the product to us. Once we have confirmed the product defect or other problem, we will:  
\- provide a full refund for any goods that are damaged or defective, if this is within a reasonable time following the sale; or  
\- at your option, repair or replace the goods at our cost (including the cost of postage), unless this would not be possible or would be disproportionately costly in the circumstances, in which case we will refund to you the amount paid by you for the goods in question.  
We will notify you of your refund via e-mail within a reasonable period of time. We will usually process the refund due to you as soon as possible and, in any case, within 14 days of the day we confirmed to you via e-mail that you were entitled to a refund for defective goods.  
We will usually refund any money received from you using the same method originally used by you to pay for your purchase.

### 9\. CANCELLATION BY US

We reserve the right to cancel the contract between us if, for example:  
\- we have insufficient stock to deliver the goods you have ordered; or  
\- one or more of the goods you ordered was listed at an incorrect price due to a typographical error  
or an error in the pricing information received by us from our suppliers.  
If we do cancel your contract we will notify you by e-mail and will re-credit to your account any sum deducted by us from your credit or debit card as soon as possible but in any event within 7 days of your order.

### 10\. TITLE AND RISK

You will become the owner of the goods you have ordered when they have been delivered to you and we have received clear funds in full payment for the goods. Once goods have been delivered to you they will be held at your own risk and we will not be liable for their loss or destruction.

### 11\. LIABILITY

We are not responsible if you cannot access the site properly or at all because of any event outside our control, for example (without limitation) the performance of your or our ISP, your browser or the internet.  
This site relies in part on software to work. Whilst we will monitor the site, we cannot guarantee that the site or any individual feature of the site will be error free, available all the time and/or free from viruses.  
It is your responsibility to implement appropriate IT security safeguards (including anti-virus and other security checks) to satisfy your particular requirements as to the safety and reliability of content.  
Nothing in these terms will affect any liability we may have: (a) for fraudulent misrepresentation; (b) for death or personal injury arising from our negligence: (c) under Part I of the Consumer  
Protection Act 1987; (d) for breach of any condition as to title or quiet enjoyment of or in relation to any goods supplied by us; or (e) in relation to any other liability, including any liabilities under sale of goods or supply of services legislation, that may not by applicable law be excluded or limited.

### 12\. EVENTS BEYOND OUR CONTROL

We will have no liability to you for any delay in delivering goods you have ordered that is caused by any event or circumstance beyond our reasonable control including, without limitation, strikes, lockouts and other industrial disputes, breakdown of systems or network access, flood, fire, explosion.

### 13\. INVALIDITY

If any part of these terms is unenforceable, the enforceability of any other part of these terms will not be affected.

### 14\. NOTICES

All notices you send us must be sent to the contact details on this site: info@brazilianbikinishop.com. We may give notice to you at either the e-mail or postal address you provide to us when making a purchase. In proving the service of any notice, it will be sufficient to prove, in the case of a letter, that the letter was properly addressed, stamped and placed in the post and, in the case of an e-mail, that the e-mail was sent to the specified e-mail address of the addressee.

## PRIVACY POLICY

We are committed to protecting your privacy on-line.  
We appreciate that you do not want the personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately and here we explain how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have.  
Who we are?  
The website is owned by Brazilian Bikini Shop and the Data Controller is Mr. Guatteri Gian Marco. The Data Controller is responsible for and controls the processing of your personal data in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act"). By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of information in accordance with this privacy policy.

### **Personal data we may collect about you**

We can only provide the goods and services ordered by you if you provide us with your personal data. For the purpose of providing these services, we collect personal data about you such as your name, address, date of birth, email address, telephone and mobile  
phone numbers.  
We will use the information you provide for the purposes described in this privacy policy to which you agreed to at the time your data was obtained. Your personal data will be used to to:  
\- Provide you with the information, goods and services offered through our website, for billing and order fulfilment  
\- (provide you with the services and information offered through our website and which you request;)  
\- administer your account with us;  
\- verify and carry out financial transactions in relation to payments you make online;  
\- audit the downloading of data from our website;  
\- improve the layout and/or content of the pages of our website and customise them for users;  
\- identify visitors to our website;  
\- carry out research on our users' demographics and tracking of sales data;  
\- send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us,  
including information about our products and services, provided you have indicated that you do not object to being contacted for these purposes;

### **Monitoring**

We may also monitor who accesses our website, for example we may automatically collect access information about you, such as the type of internet browser you use, the website from which you have come to the our website and your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognised by our web server such information enables us to assess our users, to build a profile. We also use cookies on various pages on our website. Cookies are small text files that are saved on your computer. This information does not directly identify you and for more information please also read or section entitled cookies.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (�Google�). Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site.

### **Marketing purposes:**

Subject to obtaining your consent we may contact you by by email If you prefer not to receive any marketing communications from us, you can opt out at any time. See further �Your rights� below.  
Use of cookies  
We may also obtain information about your online movements and use of the internet. We do this by placing a �cookie�, which is a small file, on your computer�s hard disk. Cookies are used for several reasons, for example to recognise you whenever you visit this website ensuring you do not have to enter all your details and thereby speeding up the process so you do not have to log on each time. It will also enable us to store your personal preferences, build a profile about you and target our marketing and advertising campaigns. We cannot provide a full service to you if you disable the cookie function on your web browser so we advise you to maintain the same.  
For further information about cookies and how to disable them please go to: aboutcookies.org  
If applicable: Disclosure of your personal data  
[choose appropriate]  
We may disclose your personal data:  
\- to other companies within our group;  
\- if we sell our business to a third party;  
\- to our agents and service providers (eg providers of web hosting or maintenance services);  
\- credit reference agents � see �Credit Reference Agencies above;  
\- in any other case where we are required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary to prevent fraud or cyber crime or to protect the website or the rights, property or personal safety of any person.  
We may also disclose aggregate statistics about visitors to our website, in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, sponsors and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will include no personally identifiable information.

### **Security**

We place great importance on the security of all personally identifiable information associated with our users. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control.  
We will use technical and organisational measures to safeguard your personal data, for example:  
\- access to your account is controlled by password and username which are unique to you;  
\- we store your personal data on secure servers;  
\- payment details are encrypted using SSL technology.  
You should bear in mind that submission of information over the internet is never entirely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of information you submit via the website whilst it is in transit over the internet and any such submission is at your own risk. All we can do is use all our reasonable efforts to safeguard your data and ensure that we maintain a reliable and safe environment to use your data.  
It is advisable to close your browser when you have finished your user session to help ensure others do not access your personal information if you use a shared computer or a computer in a public place.

### **Your rights**

If you are concerned about your data, you have the right subject to the payment of a small fee (currently $10) to request access the personal data which we may hold or process about you.  
You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge.

### **Right to prevent marketing**

At any stage you also have the right to ask us to stop using your personal data for direct marketing purposes. You can opt-out any time by sending us an email to: info@brazilianbikinishop.com

### **Our contact details**

We welcome your feedback and questions. If you wish to contact us, please send an email to  
info@brazilianbikinishop.com or or call us on (786) 224-0188
